{
    "categories": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "name": "Football",
        "questions": [
          {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "Who won the FIFA World Cup in 2018?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "France" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "Croatia" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "Brazil" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "Germany" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a"
          },
          {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "Which player has won the most Ballon d'Or awards?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "Cristiano Ronaldo" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "Lionel Messi" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "Michel Platini" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "Johan Cruyff" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b"
          },
          {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "What is the official nickname of Brazil's national football team?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "La Selección" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "Azzurri" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "Seleção" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "Les Bleus" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c"
          },
          {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "Which country hosted the FIFA World Cup in 2006?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "Germany" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "South Africa" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "Japan" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "Brazil" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a"
          },
          {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "Which club has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "FC Barcelona" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "Manchester United" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "AC Milan" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "Real Madrid" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "d"
          },
          {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "Who holds the record for the most goals in a single FIFA World Cup tournament?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "Miroslav Klose" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "Just Fontaine" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "Pele" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "Gerd Müller" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b"
          },
          {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "Which player scored the \"Hand of God\" goal?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "Diego Maradona" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "Pele" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "Zinedine Zidane" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "David Beckham" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a"
          },
          {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "In what year was the English Premier League founded?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "1988" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "1992" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "1996" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "2000" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b"
          },
          {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "What is the maximum duration of extra time in a football match?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "15 minutes" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "20 minutes" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "30 minutes" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "45 minutes" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c"
          },
          {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "Which footballer is known as \"The King\"?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "Diego Maradona" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "Lionel Messi" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "Pele" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "Cristiano Ronaldo" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c"
          },
          {
            "id": 11,
            "question": "What color cards can a referee show during a football match?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "Yellow and Green" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "Red and Green" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "Yellow and Red" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "Blue and Red" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c"
          },
          {
            "id": 12,
            "question": "Which country won the first-ever FIFA World Cup in 1930?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "Brazil" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "Uruguay" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "Argentina" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "Italy" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b"
          },
          {
            "id": 13,
            "question": "What is the regulation size of a football pitch?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "90-120 meters in length, 45-90 meters in width" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "100-130 meters in length, 50-100 meters in width" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "105-120 meters in length, 68 meters in width" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "100-110 meters in length, 65-70 meters in width" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a"
          },
          {
            "id": 14,
            "question": "Who scored the fastest goal in FIFA World Cup history?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "Hakan Şükür" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "Pelé" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "Cristiano Ronaldo" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "Zinedine Zidane" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a"
          },
          {
            "id": 15,
            "question": "Which football team is known as \"The Red Devils\"?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "Liverpool" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "Manchester United" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "Belgium National Team" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "AC Milan" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b"
          },
          {
            "id": 16,
            "question": "Which country has won the most FIFA World Cups?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "Italy" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "Germany" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "Argentina" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "Brazil" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "d"
          },
          {
            "id": 17,
            "question": "Which footballer was nicknamed \"The Divine Ponytail\"?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "Andrea Pirlo" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "Roberto Baggio" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "Francesco Totti" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "Gianfranco Zola" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b"
          },
          {
            "id": 18,
            "question": "Which country is often referred to as \"The Land of Football\"?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "Argentina" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "Brazil" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "Italy" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "England" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b"
          },
          {
            "id": 19,
            "question": "What year was the first-ever FIFA Women's World Cup held?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "1991" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "1987" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "1995" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "2000" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a"
          },
          {
            "id": 20,
            "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer in UEFA Champions League history?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "Cristiano Ronaldo" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "Lionel Messi" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "Raúl" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "Karim Benzema" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a"
          },
          {
            "id": 21,
            "question": "Which team won the first-ever Premier League title?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "Manchester United" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "Arsenal" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "Chelsea" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "Blackburn Rovers" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a"
          },
          {
            "id": 22,
            "question": "Which player scored the most goals in a calendar year?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "Lionel Messi" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "Cristiano Ronaldo" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "Pele" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "Gerd Müller" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a"
          },
          {
            "id": 23,
            "question": "Which country hosted the FIFA World Cup in 2010?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "Brazil" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "South Africa" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "Germany" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "Russia" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b"
          },
          {
            "id": 24,
            "question": "Who is the youngest player to score in a FIFA World Cup?",
            "options": [
              { "id": "a", "text": "Pelé" },
              { "id": "b", "text": "Kylian Mbappé" },
              { "id": "c", "text": "Michael Owen" },
              { "id": "d", "text": "Lionel Messi" }
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a"
          }
         ]
        }
       ]
      }  